Guide to the Hana Ginzbarg Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Armand Bayou Nature Center
  - Nature Center Planning and Protection
    - Extension of FM 2351 (2) Controversy, 1986-1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - City of Pasadena Revisions to Flood Plan Ordinance, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Federal and State Regulations on Parks and the Environment, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - State of Texas Highway Department Proposed Extension of FM 2351, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Environmental and Schematic Planning Brief FM 2351, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - An Exxon Subsidiary Against the Environment, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Brookwood Subdivision Drainage Ditch, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Brookwood Subdivision and FM 2351 Extension Controversy, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Harris County Commissioners Court Meeting Transmittal of Deed File, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Texas Parks and Wildlife Department, Baywood Country Club, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Public Proposal of a Proposed Hazardous Waste Exemption, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Brookwood Subdivision Storm Water Runoff, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Kipper Mease Sports Complex Controversy, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Nature Center Management
    - Armand Bayou Survey Locations, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Nature Center Expansion, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Book Presentation to Courts, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Armand Bayou Nature Center Plan of Action, Oct 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Acquisition Tract 7, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Acquisition Tract 10 and 11 (1), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Acquisition Tract 10 and 11 (2), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Harris County Lease Agreements, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Armand Bayou Designation as a Bicentennial Horizon Project, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Preservation of Historic Archeological Sites at Armand Bayou, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Preservation of Historic Archeological Sites at Armand Bayou, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Long Term Objectives of Armand Bayou Nature Center, Inc., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Landscaping and Trail Improvements, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 5 Year Plan Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Armand Bayou Plan by Hana N. Ginzbarg, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Long Term Planning Committee Meeting, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Maps Brookwood Subdivision, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Master Plan Proposal for Immediate Physical Development, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Nature Center Publications
    - Armand Bayou Park and Nature Center, March 1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Armand Bayou Nature Center Inc., Winter 1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Armand Bayou Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Natural History Guide to Armand Bayou Nature Center, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - “A Texas Tea Dance”, Armand Bayou 10th Anniversary Dinner Invitation, March 1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Martyn Farm Fall Festival Mailer, October 1986 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Welcome to My Home at Armand Bayou Nature Center Mailer, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Winter Camp, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Various Armand Bayou Pamphlets, undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Armand Bayou Brochures, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Template for Armand Bayou Brochure, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Armand Bayou Nature Center Letterhead, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Preservation of Armand Bayou Committee Letterhead, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Fall Program, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Spring Program, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Fall Program, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Spring Newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Summer Newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Fall Newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Winter Newsletter, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Spring Newsletter, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Summer Newsletter, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Winter Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Fall Newsletter, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bayou Foliage, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Nature Center Advocate Organizations
    - Bayou Preservation Association Inc. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Citizens Who Care (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Conference of the Bureau of Recreation “Recreation in the Coastal Zone", March 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Houston Audubon Society (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Houston League of Women Voters (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Natural Resources Advisory Committee (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - The Park People (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Photographs
    - Collage Photographs, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - The Christening of the Hana G. Boat and Ground Breaking of the Nature Center, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Brookwood Subdivision, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Ft. Worth Nature Center and Refuge, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Nature Center Publicity
    - Clippings, January 1974-March 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Clippings, April 1974-June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Clippings, July 1974-December 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Clippings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Clippings, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Clippings, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Clippings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Clippings, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Clippings, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Clippings, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Clippings Bayou Interpretive Guide Program, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Clippings-Harris County’s Role, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - New Director for Armand Bayou Nature Center Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Clippings FM 2351 Controversy, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - American Motors Conservation Award to Hana Ginzbarg, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - San Jacinto College Student Report on Armand Bayou, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Houston Chronicle Magazine, October 20, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Exxon USA Magazine, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Houston City Magazine, June 1978 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Texas Highways, February 1982 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - National Conservation Awards Program, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - KUHT Pamphlet Armand Bayou: An Urban Wilderness, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - KUHT Armand Bayou: An Urban Wilderness VHS Cassette, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Wetlands-EPA and CEC, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Sierra Club Bayou Banner, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - The William Dobie Survey Harris County, Texas, undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Taped Interview Papers, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Armand Bayou Movie Script, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Lists and Articles Regarding the Natural History of Armand Bayou, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Time Life Books, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - TV Contacts, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Artifacts
    - “The Big Adventure” Button, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - “Save Armand Bayou Again…” Bumper Sticker, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Nature Center Notes and Information
    - Notes (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Media Contacts, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Maps (OVS)
  - Aerial Map Clear Lake and Vicinity, 1971 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - Clear Lake City Area Map, May 1973 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - Clear Lake City Water Authority Map, May-June 1969 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - Topography and Site Development Map, 1974 (Box 9, Item 4)
  - New Home Journal, Volume 1, Number 3, 1987 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - Pasadena and Baytown Vicinity Maps, 1989 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - Armand Bayou Land Tract Map, undated (Box 9, Item 7)
  - Armand Bayou Topographic Map, 1987 (Box 9, Item 8)
  - Armand Bayou Map, undated (Box 9, Item 9)